Maroua Majdoub

Computer Science Engineering student in https://www.linkedin.com/in/maroua-majdoub/

majdoub.maroua2001@gmail.com

L+39 3514676423

• Via Cavour 9A, Casei Gerola, Italy

Passionate Computer Science and Applied Mathematics Engineering student with international experience, alternating studies between Italy and Tunisia, dedicated to pushing the boundaries of technological advancement. Committed to continuous learning and growth, I thrive in collaborative environments where I can contribute my diverse skills and perspectives. Excited to embark on a journey of innovation and make a lasting impact.

Experience

• Graphic Designer

PYFAC 9.0 | pitch yourself for a career

2023-2024

Worked together with the design team, utilizing a diverse array of tools including Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, and Adobe Premiere Pro to create captivating visual assets such as social media posts, logos, banners, and video content. Our workflow was organized through Trello, where we efficiently managed project tasks.

• Web developer intern

ProgidyInfoTEch

2023-2024

Contributed to building responsive websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JavaScript.

Side Projects

• Travel agency Website Developed travel agency website with booking features using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

• Restaurant mobile Application

Built restaurant mobile app on Android using Java and Firebase, enabling easy ordering and reservations.

Certifications

Scrum Fundamentals Certified SFC

ScrumStudy

• Responsive Web Design

Freecodecamp

• JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Freecodecamp

Education

National Engineering School of Sfax ,Tunisia

2023-present

During my academic journey, I acquired invaluable knowledge in Algorithms and problem solving using c,c++ and Java, delved into SQL and explored the world of Computer vision with OpenCV.

• Preparatory Engineering Institute of Monastir, Tunisia

2021-2022

Associative life

Project Manager

IEEE Woman in engineering affinity group

Microsoft Tech Club

IEEE

Member

IEEEXtreme 17.0 programming competition

 Participant Designer

Member

GAITA: summer school on generative intelligence

skills

- Soft skills: Project Management, teamwork, effective communication, time management, leadership
- **Programming languages:** c,c++,Java,Python
- Database: PL/SOL ,oracle
- Web development: HTML,CSS,JavaScript,Bootstrap,ReactJS,Agile Scrum
- Design: Adobe illustrator, Figma, Adobe premier pro
- Control version: Git/Github https://github.com/marwamajdoub

Languages

 English Fluent

- French Fluent
- German basic

Fluent Italian

- Arabic native
- Hobbies and Interest

Sport, Art, Travel, Reading